in this lesson we're going to explore
在这一课中 我们将探索
brush customization in more detail when
在以下情况下更详细地自定义画笔
creating brushes everything you will
创建笔刷可以将您想要的一切
need can be found in the brush editor
可以在画笔编辑器中找到需要的内容
panel expand the brush editor panel to
面板展开画笔编辑器面板以
show all of the properties available but
显示所有可用的属性 但是
try to conserve any wasted space this
尽量节省任何浪费的空间
panel makes it easy to modify the brush
面板使修改画笔变得很容易
properties while previewing those
属性 同时预览
changes in real time with the stroke
随着笔划的实时变化
preview you can also paint onto your
预览您还可以在您的
canvas to evaluate the brushes while
画布来评估画笔 同时
you'll be doing the bulk of your brush
你将会做你的大部分刷子
modification through the brush editor
通过画笔编辑器进行修改
the brush engines Define the
画笔引擎定义了
capabilities of the brush so that's
刷子的性能 所以这是
where you want to start when you're
你想从哪里开始 当你
creating a brush from scratch it can be
从头开始创建画笔可以是
helpful to imagine that the brush you're
想象一下你的画笔很有帮助
creating is an animal the brush engines
创造是刷子引擎的动物
are where I can change a bird to a
我可以把一只鸟变成一只鸟
mammal or a mammal to a reptile these
哺乳动物或哺乳动物对爬行动物的这些
would be big drastic changes to the
将是一个巨大的巨大的变化
behavior and appearance of the animal or
动物或动物的行为和外表
brush the changes made in the brush
笔刷在画笔中所做的更改
editor can be more subtle in comparison
相比之下 编辑可以更微妙
for example changing a pigeon to a
例如 将一只鸽子更改为
parrot or a parrot to an ostrich in
一只鹦鹉或一只鹦鹉给鸵鸟
Brush terms I could turn a pencil into
画笔术语我可以把一支铅笔变成
charcoal with the brush editor but I
用画笔编辑木炭 但我
wouldn't be able to change charcoal to a
不能把木炭改成
deformation brush that smudges pixels
涂抹像素的变形笔刷
unless I start with a different brush
除非我从不同的画笔开始
engine unfortunately it's not as simple
引擎 不幸的是 它不是那么简单
as it could be to change the brush
就像换刷子一样
engine of a brush what you'll need to do
刷子的引擎你需要做什么
is first select a default brush that is
是首先选择一个默认画笔
using that engine and build your new
使用该引擎并构建您的新
brush from that you can use the panel on
从那里你可以使用画笔的面板
the left to filter out brushes that use
左侧用于过滤使用的笔刷
specific brush
专用刷子
engines let's start by exploring the
引擎让我们从探索
contents of the brush editor as we
笔刷编辑器的内容
looked at in early lessons this panel is
在早期的课程中看到了这个小组是
going to show you all of the relevant
我将向您展示所有相关的
properties for the currently selected
当前选定的
brush the contents will change depending
笔刷内容将根据不同而变化
on the brush engine you have selected
在您选择的画笔引擎上
these properties are divided by sections
这些属性按部分进行划分
for General color texture and masked
用于常规颜色纹理和蒙版
brush within those categories are the
这些类别中的画笔是
properties each with numerous options
每个酒店都有许多选择
sliders and buttons that control
控制的滑块和按钮
specific aspects of the brush nearest
画笔最接近的特定方面
the top are the general properties brush
顶部是常规属性画笔
tip blending mode opacity and flow these
提示混合模式不透明度和流动这些
are un unversal properties that can be
是可以被
applied to many types of brushes though
适用于多种类型的刷子
some of the specialty brush engines have
一些特殊的刷子引擎有
their own unique set of properties you
他们自己的一组独特的属性
may notice that some of the properties
可能会注意到一些物业
are grayed out this is because these
是灰色的 这是因为这些
properties are not applicable to the
属性不适用于
currently selected brush the indented
当前选定的笔刷缩进
properties are more advanced you'll need
属性更高级 您将需要
to enable these by clicking first to the
要启用这些功能 请先单击
left of the name if you see a check the
名称左侧 如果您看到复选标记
property has been applied to your brush
属性已应用于您的画笔
I can change the size spacing rotation
我可以更改大小间距旋转
scatter and other properties that affect
散布和影响的其他属性
the dab shape there's also a category of
这个不错的形状还有一类
color properties which control the color
控制颜色的颜色属性
of your brush Media or what comes out of
您的画笔介质或从
your brush you can lighten darken or
你的刷子你可以变浅变暗或
vary the Hue of your color as well as
改变你的颜色的色调以及
control the buildup and mixing of colors
控制颜色的组合和混合
the texture properties contain the
纹理属性包含
various textures that you can apply to
可以应用于的各种纹理
dabs this is a key feature for brush
Dabs这是笔刷的关键功能
creation because it can really add a lot
创造 因为它真的可以增加很多东西
of character to your brushes and the
你的画笔和
Mast brush properties which are only
母版画笔属性仅为
applicable to the pixel brush engine
适用于像素笔刷引擎
will allow you to Overlay a second dab
将允许您覆盖第二个DAB
on top of your brush to create more
在画笔顶部创建更多
intricate get
复杂的Get
strokes because C's brush settings are
笔划 因为C的笔刷设置是
so extensive I won't be able to cover
范围如此之广 我无法涵盖
absolutely every combination of
绝对是每一种
properties that the brush editor is
画笔编辑器的属性
capable of it's a lot but I am going to
有能力做到这一点很多 但我会
teach you the fundamentals so that you
教你基础知识 这样你就能
can experiment to discover the extent of
可以通过实验来发现
what it can do it would take a very long
它能做的事情需要很长时间
time to try every possible combination
是时候尝试所有可能的组合了
of brush properties in Crea by the time
时 Crea中的笔刷属性
you finally did Crea probably would have
你终于做到了Crea可能会
changed and added new features that may
更改并添加了可能
sound frustrating but that's actually a
听起来令人沮丧 但这实际上是
good thing it means that there is a lot
好消息是这意味着有很多
of room to innovate and discover new
创新和发现新事物的空间
brushes I am able to create unique
我可以创造独一无二的画笔
brushes that no one has ever used and
没有人用过的刷子
that feels really
那感觉真的很棒
cool I'll select the basic five size
太好了 我要基本的五号
brush and if we look in general size we
刷子 如果我们看起来一般大小 我们
can see that enable pen settings is
可以看到启用笔设置是
checked pressure is selected beneath
在下面选择了检查的压力
that which indicates that the pen
表明这支笔
pressure I use when pressing on my
当我按压我的
tablet will determine the size of the
平板电脑将决定
brush you can use the graph to control
画笔你可以用图形来控制
how much size variation you get when you
当您在执行以下操作时 您会得到多大的尺寸变化
press down with your pen the horizontal
用你的钢笔按下水平线
axis is how hard you are pressing from
轴是你按压的力度
low to high the vertical axis is size
从低到高垂直轴的大小
variation from small to large pressure
从小到大的变化
is the most common way to control the
是控制
size property but just to explain how
Size属性 但只是为了解释如何
these settings work let's choose tilt
这些设置起作用 让我们选择倾斜
Direction and disable pressure now when
在以下情况下立即指示和禁用压力
I tilt my pen in each Direction I can
我尽可能地朝每个方向倾斜我的钢笔
vary the brush size pressure doesn't do
改变画笔大小压力不起作用
anything you'll find these brush
你能找到的任何东西都是这些刷子
expressions in many of the properties
在许多属性中的表达式
and you can control them in the same
你可以在同一个平台上控制它们
manner I'll set this back to pressure St
我会把这个调回加压状态
Str is set to 100% this controls how
Str设置为100% 这将控制如何
much the size will vary when I use
当我使用的时候 尺寸会有很大的变化
pressure If I make a stroke from light
如果我从光中划出一击 就会受到压力
to heavy you can see a lot of variation
变重了 你可以看到很多变化
if I set the strength lower you can see
如果我把强度调低 你会看到
that range is reduced so strength will
这一范围被缩小了 所以力量将
work in the same way for the other
以同样的方式为对方工作
properties as well I'll disable size and
属性 我将禁用大小和
let's look under opacity next this
接下来让我们在不透明下查看
controls the opacity of The Strokes
控制笔划的不透明度
currently my strokes and dabs are fully
目前 我的划水和拍打都已经满了
opaque but if I reduce the strength then
不透明 但如果我降低强度
I can make semi-transparent Strokes and
我可以制作半透明的笔触和
dabs I'll set it back to 100% if I
Dabs我会把它调回100%如果我
enable pin settings and set it to
启用PIN设置并将其设置为
pressure then I can press lightly to
然后我就可以轻轻地按到
make my Strokes more transparent heavy
使我的笔触更透明、更厚重
pressure will make them more opaque I
压力会让他们更不透明
can even combine size with opacity to
甚至可以将大小和不透明度结合在一起
get both Expressions
同时获取两个表达式
simultaneously flow is similar to
同时流动类似于
opacity but it controls the opacity of
不透明度 但它控制
each dab on the stroke rather than the
每次轻拍笔触 而不是
stroke as a hole I'll disable opacity
笔划为洞 我将禁用不透明度
for some brushes you may want to change
对于某些刷子 您可能需要更换
the flow to make the brush build up more
使画笔建立更多的流
slowly but in this case it creates
缓慢 但在这种情况下 它创建了
unsightly artifacts where the dabs and
难看的文物在那里的抹布和
strokes
笔画
overlap I'll enable scatter next this
重叠我将启用散布下一步
will offset the position of some of the
将抵消一些
dabs to break up the stroke a little
轻轻拍打 让划水稍稍散开
scatter will give you a jagged line a
散布会给你一条参差不齐的线
high scatter value will create a spray
较高的散布值将产生喷雾
or splatter effect and again I can
或飞溅效应 我再一次可以
control the scattering distance with
使用控制散射距离
expressions like
像这样的表达
pressure if I set the flow strength back
如果我将流动强度调回 则压力
to 100% softness can be useful to make
到100%柔软度可以用来制作
your brush dab and strokes softer along
你的刷子轻拍 笔触更柔和
the edges this can help give the
这有助于为
appearance of a wetter medium a low
出现较潮湿的中低气压
value will give you the softest
价值会带给你最柔软的
edges spacing is another important
边间距是另一个重要的因素
property this controls the distance
属性该属性控制距离
between each dab and a stroke a low
在每一次轻拍和一次击球之间
value works best to create a continuous
价值最有效地创造了一个连续的
stroke a high value works best for
笔划的值越高越好
creating a dashed line or a spray brush
创建虚线或喷雾笔刷
any brushes that have had their
任何刷子都有过他们的
properties edited will show a pencil
编辑的属性将显示一支铅笔
icon in the brush presets panel
画笔预设面板中的图标
resetting a brush to its default is
将画笔重置为其默认设置为
quite easy just click either on the
非常简单 只需点击
reset button in the brush editor or the
笔刷编辑器中的“重置”按钮或
properties
属性
bar let's move back up to brush tip this
酒吧 让我们回到笔尖上来
gives you control over the dab of your
让您可以控制您的
brush for Pixel engine brushes you can
像素引擎笔刷 您可以
choose from Auto predefined or text
从自动预定义或文本中选择
we'll only use the first two options
我们将只使用前两个选项
Auto can automatically generate dab
Auto可以自动生成DAB
shapes you can choose from circular or
可以从圆形或圆形中选择形状
Square dabs change the edge hardness dab
方形点数改变边缘硬度点数
flatness and dab angle and create
平整度和轻拍角度 并创建
Speckles within each dab to simulate
要模拟的每个DAB中的斑点
bristles
刚毛
for a more intricate dab you can choose
如果想要更复杂的涂抹 你可以选择
predefined this will let you pick from a
预定义的这将允许您从一个
number of dab shapes and you can even
许多轻拍形状 你甚至可以
import your own either by drawing them
通过绘制它们来导入您自己的
on the canvas and making a selection
在画布上并进行选择
around them or by saving them as a file
或通过将它们保存为文件
there are spacing settings here too this
这里也有间距设置 这个
works independently of the other spacing
独立于其他间距工作
property which is sort of extra spacing
属性 它是一种额外的空格
that can be controlled with an
可以通过一个
expression like pressure don't set the
像压力这样的表达不会设定
value of the main spacing too low or
主间距的值太小或
you'll create excessive dabs that will
你会创造出过多的Dabs
cause the brush to lag I'll reset the
使画笔滞后 我将重置
brush again painting with flat brushes
用平画笔再刷一遍画
can be very useful just think about how
是非常有用的 只要想想
many flat traditional brushes there are
那里有许多平坦的传统画笔
to flatten a dab you can either make
要使涂抹变平 您可以制作
your own predefined dab or use the auto
您自己预定义的DAB或使用AUTO
mode under Auto I'll use a circular dab
自动模式下 我将使用圆形轻拍
and reduce the ratio to flatten the dab
并降低比率以使DAB变平
next I'll add a rotation property and
接下来 我将添加一个旋转属性和
set it to tilt Direction now I can angle
将其设置为倾斜方向 现在我可以倾斜角度
my pen to change the angle of the dab as
我的钢笔将轻拍的角度改为
you can see I can easily make thick and
你可以看到我可以很容易地变得稠密和
thin Strokes should you you need to
轻描淡写应该是你需要的
change the starting angle of the dab you
更改轻拍的起始角度
can do that in the brush tip under
可以在画笔笔尖下做到这一点
angle the blending mode properties
混合模式属性的角度
control how your brush medium blends
控制画笔介质的混合方式
with underlying colors does it simply
用底色 是不是很简单
cover them opaquely or does it tint
用不透明的遮盖物遮盖 还是有色？
darker like ink or watercolor would if
像墨水或水彩这样的深色如果
it's the lad then multiply or burn works
这是小伙子 然后乘法或烧毁工作
well to give you this effect in a sense
好的 在某种意义上给你这个效果
this property is able to change the
此属性能够更改
medium that comes out of your brush
从你的刷子里出来的中等大小
there are many more modes which give you
有更多的模式可以为您提供
non-traditional effects as well for
非传统效果也适用于
example you can build up glowing lights
例如 您可以设置发光的灯光
with screen or color Dodge with this
用屏幕或彩色减淡
brush the blending mode affects the
笔刷混合模式会影响
blending of each stroke but there's
每一种笔划的混合 但有
another way it can work which I will
另一种我会做的工作方式
come back to in a second I'll set the
回来吧 我马上就把
blending mode back to normal which is
混合模式恢复为正常模式
the default opaque paint next we'll move
默认的不透明油漆下一步我们将移动
on to the color properties here you'll
在此处的颜色属性上 您将
find more properties that can affect the
查找更多可能影响
color of the brush medium painting mode
画笔介质绘制模式的颜色
can also affect how the blending mode
还会影响混合模式的方式
works wash gives you a glazing effect
Works洗涤给你一种上光的效果
where your dabs do not build up upon
在那里你的乳房不是建立在
each other to to see what I mean I'll
为了明白我的意思 我会
use the multiply blending mode again
再次使用倍增混合模式
when I overlap Strokes with both modes
当我用两种模式重叠笔划时
you can see how the effect builds up
你可以看到效果是如何积累起来的
more rapidly and yields more unsightly
速度更快 产量更难看
artifacts when I use buildup for many
当我为许多人使用积木时出现的人工制品
mediums like marker you may want it to
像记号笔这样的媒介 你可能想让它
build up rapidly but for others where
建设迅速 但对其他人来说
you want to overlap a stroke with more
您希望将笔划与更多笔划重叠
control over the opacity wash is the way
控制不透明度洗涤是一种方法
to
至
go the source property can drastically
使用源属性可以极大地
change the medium that comes out of your
更改从您的计算机中产生的介质
brush for example it's set to plain
例如 它被设置为普通画笔
color for now but I can also get a
现在是彩色的 但我也可以买到
variety of effects using gradients noise
使用渐变噪波的各种效果
and patterns now instead of painting my
和图案 而不是画我的
Strokes I'm getting something more
我得到了更多的东西
exotic in the middle there are a bunch
异国情调的中间有一堆
of color modes that can be applied to
可应用于的颜色模式的
your brush I'll reset this brush these
你的刷子我要把这个刷子重置一下
color properties are similar to The
颜色属性类似于
blending mode but rather than affecting
混合模式 但不影响
underlying colors on the canvas they
画布上的基本颜色
only affect the color of the dabs if I
仅在以下情况下影响DAB的颜色
enable any of these I can also enable
启用其中任何一项我也可以启用
pin settings to control the effects with
用于控制效果的PIN设置
pressure or other Expressions I won't go
压力或其他表达方式我不会去的
over over all of these but let's try
所有这些 但让我们试一试
darken so we can see how it is supposed
变暗 这样我们就能看到它应该是如何
to work I'll reduce the strength a bit
为了工作 我会减少一点力量
with my expression set to pen pressure I
随着我的表情设置为笔压我
can make light strokes and they appear
可以轻描淡写 然后它们就会出现
as my selected color but once I begin to
作为我选择的颜色 但一旦我开始
increase pressure my paint will begin to
加大压力我的油漆就会开始
gradually darken these tend to give you
逐渐变暗这些往往会给你
unnatural effects but there are some
不自然的影响 但有一些
traditional media effects you can get as
您可以获得的传统媒体效果
well if you experiment it is possible to
嗯 如果你做实验 就有可能
combine blending modes with these dab
将混合模式与这些轻拍相结合
color modes as well we'll skip past
颜色模式也一样 我们将跳过
airbrush and r and move on to the next
喷枪和r 然后移动到下一个
category the next set of properties can
类别 则下一组属性可以
add texture to your brushes I'll reset
给你的画笔添加纹理 我会重置的
this brush and under pattern I'll first
这把刷子和下面的图案我先来
enable it then select one of these
启用它 然后选择以下选项之一
dotted patterns when I paint on the
当我在上面画的时候 我画的是点图案
canvas you can see that pattern
画布你可以看到那个图案
subtracted from my paint this is meant
从我的画中减去这意味着
to simulate the effect you'd get while
以模拟您将获得的效果
working on a textured Canvas OR with a
在有纹理的画布上工作或使用
textured medium like chalk charcoal or
质感介质 如粉笔、木炭或
pastel I will be covering texture in its
粉彩I将覆盖纹理在它的
own section so for now I won't say
自己的部分 所以现在我不会说
anything else about it m brush is
关于它的任何其他方面 我的画笔都是
something we will come back to in that
我们会在那篇文章中再谈到的
lesson as well I know that was a lot to
同样的教训我知道这对我来说太难了
take in but the good news is that unless
但好消息是 除非
you were creating brushes you need not
您正在创建不需要的画笔
touch many of the properties in the
触摸中的许多属性
brush editor it's okay to tweak these
画笔编辑可以调整这些
properties here and there but if you
属性 但如果您
find you're changing properties often
发现您经常更改属性
consider making multiple brush variants
考虑制作多个画笔变体
instead because it could be more
相反 因为它可能会有更多
efficient when creating a brush from
使用创建画笔时的效率
scratch start with the brush engine then
先从画笔引擎开始 然后
refine the brush with the brush editor
使用笔刷编辑器优化笔刷
you can choose any of the default cre
您可以选择任何默认cre
brushes and then use them as a starting
刷子 然后用它们作为起点
point let's create a bristly looking
让我们来创造一个看起来毛茸茸的
brush with thick oily paint from scratch
用厚厚的油性油漆从头开始刷
so you can see the process I'll start
所以你可以看到我要开始的过程
with basic five size and reset it I want
基本的五码和重置 我想要
to customize the shape of the dab first
首先自定义DAB的形状
so let's choose brush chip predefined
所以让我们选择预定义的刷子芯片
bristle Circle
刷毛圆圈
sparse now it has a different bristly
现在稀疏了 它有了不同的刚毛
appearance the spacing is too high so I
外观间距太大了 所以我
will decrease it just enough to where I
会把它降到刚刚好的程度
get a continuous
获得一个连续的
line I'd like to utilize textur as well
线条 我也想用纹理
so let's enable it and add wo texture
所以让我们启用它并添加两个纹理
now I get a canvas effect to make the
现在我得到了一种画布效果来使
bristles not so repetitive I'll also add
刷毛不是那么重复 我还会加上
a rotation property and set it to tilt
旋转属性 并将其设置为倾斜
Direction now when I tilt my pen the
方向现在当我倾斜我的笔的时候
bristle dab
毛茸茸的轻拍
rotates now that I have defined the
旋转 因为我已经定义了
basic look and behavior of my brush I
我的画笔的基本外观和行为是
can begin to fine-tune it I think I'm
可以开始微调了 我想我是
happy with the shape of the brush so
对画笔的形状很满意 所以
I'll refine the brush media I want
我会改进我想要的画笔介质
pressure to control the opacity of the
控制不透明度的压力
paint so I'll add that now the paint
油漆 所以我现在要加上油漆
looks a little wetter while the brush in
刷进去的时候看起来有点湿
you've chosen tends to have the most
你所选择的往往拥有最多
dramatic impact on the look of a brush
对刷子外观的戏剧性影响
with the right settings the properties
通过正确的设置 这些属性
in the brush editor can make some
在画笔编辑器中可以制作一些
extreme changes as well for instance I
极端的变化也是如此 例如
can add some scatter to change this from
我可以添加一些散布来改变这种情况
a single bristly stroke to a brush that
刷子上的一笔毛发
makes fine splatters this barely
几乎不会造成这么好的飞溅
resembles the previous version of this
类似于此的前一个版本
brush however the behavior of the media
然而 对媒体的行为不以为然
Remains the Same it's still wet looking
还是老样子 看起来还是湿的
opaque
不透明
paint that should give you a pretty good
油漆应该会给你一个很好的
overview of how the brush engines work
笔刷引擎工作原理概述
alongside the brush editor
在画笔编辑器旁边
in order to save this brush for later
为了保存此画笔以备以后使用
use you can save a new brush preset give
使用您可以保存的新笔刷预设
the brush a unique name so you can
画笔有一个唯一的名称 这样你就可以
differentiate it from the default brush
将其与默认画笔区分开来
you can add a custom thumbnail as well
您也可以添加自定义缩略图
either create the thumbnail first and
或者先创建缩略图 然后
save it as an image file or paint
将其保存为图像文件或绘画
directly onto the thumbnail area with
直接放到缩略图区域上
your chosen color since the dab and
你选择的颜色 因为轻拍和
stroke previews are not always helpful
笔划预览并不总是有用的
the name can also help to remind you of
这个名字也会让你想起
the brush Behavior or your intention
画笔行为或您的意图
when you created it after saving you may
在保存后创建它时 您可以
want to tag the brush to add it to a
我想标记画笔以将其添加到
category I recommend resetting the
类别我建议重置
original brush you started with when you
您开始时使用的原始画笔
are
是
finished you can always rename your
完成后 您可以随时重命名您的
brushes at any time simply click on the
画笔在任何时候只需点击
pencil icon in the brush Editor to
笔刷编辑器中的铅笔图标以
change
变化
it the changes you make to brushes will
如果您对画笔所做的更改将
be reflected in the Creed resource files
反映在Creed资源文件中
so if you want to keep your brushes
所以如果你想保留你的画笔
backed up you'll need to copy them once
备份后 您需要复制它们一次
they have been completed if you don't
如果你不这样做 它们已经完成了
want to always have to remember to
想要永远记住
manually back up your brushes you can
可以手动备份您的画笔
also do it automatically using something
也可以使用某些东西自动完成此操作
like Dropbox or one drive to back up
例如要备份的Dropbox或一个驱动器
your cre library on a regular
定期更新您的cre图书馆
basis managing brushes and cre can be
基础管理笔刷和cre可以是
difficult compared to other art
与其他艺术相比 难度更大
applications any brushes you create will
应用程序您创建的任何笔刷都将
be based off of existing brushes and
基于现有画笔和
will be saved into the library or bundle
将保存到库或捆绑包中
that brush is located in in this case
在这种情况下 该画笔位于
the brush I created was in the local
我创建的画笔是在本地
resources so to view the file I can go
资源 所以要查看文件 我可以
to settings manage resources and then
设置管理资源 然后
open resource folder look in paint op
打开资源文件夹在绘制中查找操作
presets and you'll see any new brushes
预置 你会看到任何新的画笔
and tags you created there it's
和你在那里创建的标签
important to note that if you created
请务必注意 如果您创建了
any custom brush tips those need to go
任何定制的笔刷笔尖都需要
along with the brush presets if you move
以及笔刷预设(如果您移动
backup or share them these can be found
备份或共享它们可以找到
in the brushes folder deleting brushes
在笔刷文件夹中删除笔刷
is not very straightforward either you
你也不是很直截了当
need to do it from the manage resources
我需要从管理资源中执行此操作
dialogue I can remove anything here
对话我可以删除这里的任何内容
including brush tips bundles are library
包括笔尖的捆绑包都是库
of resources that can package content
可以打包内容的资源
together it can be tedious to create a
在一起 创建一个
bundle since you have to select all of
捆绑包 因为您必须选择所有
the content individually if you disable
如果禁用 则会单独显示内容
some of the bundles you aren't copying
您没有复制的某些捆绑包
content from that makes it easier to
其中的内容使其更容易
sort through as you can see I've created
整理一下 你可以看到我已经创建了
my own bundle with my custom brushes in
我自己的捆绑包和我的定制刷子
it you can install this on your computer
如果您可以在您的计算机上安装此程序
if you like the file can be found in the
如果您喜欢 可以在
resource files if you purchase the paid
如果您购买付费的资源文件
course moving brushes and content
课程移动画笔和内容
between bundles is tricky as well
捆绑包之间也很棘手
technically a bundle file can be
从技术上讲 捆绑包文件可以
duplicated and renamed to a zip file and
复制并重命名为压缩文件 并
you can access the content within this
您可以访问此中的内容
can be helpful to extract brushes and
可以帮助提取笔刷和
other types of files
其他类型的文件
if you collect everything in your local
如果你在当地收集所有的东西
resources folder by copying or importing
通过复制或导入的资源文件夹
it you can easily save a new bundle with
通过它 您可以轻松保存新的捆绑包
that content in
其中的内容
it to delete bundles and remove them
它需要删除捆绑包并移除它们
from CRE instead of just making them
来自CRE而不是仅仅制作它们
inactive you must delete the bundle file
非活动状态 您必须删除捆绑包文件
in your resources folder just be sure
在您的资源文件夹中 只需确保
those files are backed up if you don't
如果您不这样做 这些文件将被备份
want to permanently lose
想要永远失去
them
他们